 [
    {"category" : "Database-Systems",
    "question" : "What is a database?",
    "correct_answer" : "Organized collection of data or information that can be accessed, updated, and managed" ,
    "incorrect_answers" : ["Organized collection of information that cannot be accessed, updated, and managed", "Collection of data or information without organizing", "Organized collection of data that cannot be updated"] },
    {"category" : "Database-Systems",
    "question" : "Which type of data can be stored in the database?",
    "correct_answer" : "All of the other options" ,
    "incorrect_answers" : ["Image oriented data", "Text, files containing data", "Data in the form of audio or video"] },
    {"category" : "Database-Systems",
    "question" : "_________________ operations do not preserve non-matched tuples.?",
    "correct_answer" : "Inner join" ,
    "incorrect_answers" : ["Left outer join", "Natural join", "Right outer join"] },
    {"category" : "Database-Systems",
    "question" : "The ability to query data, as well as insert, delete, and alter tuples, is offered by ____________",
    "correct_answer" : "DML (Data Manipulation Langauge)" ,
    "incorrect_answers" : ["TCL (Transaction Control Language)", "DCL (Data Control Language)", "DDL (Data Definition Langauge)"] },
    {"category" : "Database-Systems",
    "question" : "What do you mean by one to many relationships?",
    "correct_answer" : "One teacher can have many classes" ,
    "incorrect_answers" : ["One class may have many teachers", "Many classes may have many teachers", "Many teachers may have many classes"] },
    {"category" : "Database-Systems",
    "question" : "Which of the following refers to the number of tuples in a relation?",
    "correct_answer" : "Cardinality" ,
    "incorrect_answers" : ["Entity", "Column", "None of the others"] },
    {"category" : "Database-Systems",
    "question" : "Which one of the following is a type of Data Manipulation Command?",
    "correct_answer" : "Delete" ,
    "incorrect_answers" : ["Create", "Alter", "All of the others"] },
    {"category" : "Database-Systems",
    "question" : "Which one of the following refers to the total view of the database content?",
    "correct_answer" : "Conceptual view" ,
    "incorrect_answers" : ["Physical view", "Internal view", "External view"] },
    {"category" : "Database-Systems",
    "question" : "Which of the following keys is generally used to represents the relationships between the tables?",
    "correct_answer" : "Foreign key" ,
    "incorrect_answers" : ["Primary key", "Secondary key", "None of the others"] },
    {"category" : "Database-Systems",
    "question" : "Which one of the following keyword is used to find out the number of values in a column?",
    "correct_answer" : "COUNT" ,
    "incorrect_answers" : ["TOTAL", "SUM", "ADD"] }
 ]

